ANN MARIA GEORGE

gann782@gmail.com 9961627268

Kerala, India

SUMMARY

I have an overall experience of 5+ years in the field of Client engagement, recruitment and data management. I have an MBA and the project specializes in HR. I am seeking to find a suitable role in a reputed organization. I have been an expertise in communication with international clients and have the understanding of people Management.

KEY SKILLS

Excellent Interpersonal skills • Adaptability • Quick Learner Communication skills • Recruitment • Problem solving

TECHNICAL SKILLS

MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ENVERTIZ CONSULTANCY

Jul 2023- Present

Sourcing Coordinator

Kochi

- Ensures to hire the ideal candidates as per the client requirements
- Helps in Preparatory sessions sent via email to candidates
- Communicating with the candidate via phone and ensuring that their preferences are met and allocating them accordingly

ALLIANZ Aug 2021-Aug 2022

Senior Customer Service Associate

Trivandrum

- Helps in assisting stock market value and other data related concerns about their product purchase
- Advises clients in terms of their Retirement plan invested in the stock market and its changes
- Ensures valid information after verifying authenticity of clients

PETROLINK PRIVATE LTD.

May 2019-Dec 2019

Data Operator Kochi

- Assists clients in Troubleshooting queries faced by them while using the application
- Processing of documents includes creating previews for attachments for easy review and creating PDF files for attachments that require proprietary software to open
- •Processes data by reviewing and managing documents as per client requirements

NORTHGATE ARINSO HUMAN RESOURCE

Jun 2016- Dec 2018

Associate Kochi

- · Worked as an agent in examining valid documents to provide Educational reimbursement
- Ensures reimbursement were only given to the eligible criteria met by candidates
- Processing payments to Retired Employees by encashing their remaining leave balance

- Assists clients in career development with the help of courses offered by bank
- Researching the data given in SAP and accordingly processing payments

RR DONNELLY Aug 2014- Aug 2015

Associate Trivandrum

- Worked as an agent in analyzing and recording transactions given by customer
- Billing customers using SAP
- Assisting customers by giving accurate information regarding their property and water supply

KG INFORMATION SYSTEMS PRIVATE LTD.

Jun 2013-Dec 2013

Junior Recruiter Coimbatore

- Worked and assisted candidates in the initial screening process for their recruitment requirements
- Worked with their division ENTER MARKETING in assisting and collecting data for their recruitment purpose Sourcing and screening of potential candidates for contract, contract-to-hire and permanent openings with our clients
- Learning and understanding job requirements from the client and assisting them in hiring a suitable candidate according to their requirements
- Focusing on assisting suitable candidates with their goals and expectations

EDUCATION

LIVERPOOL JOHN MOORES UNIVERSITY

Mar 2021-Mar 2022

Master's in Business Administration (Distant Education)

United Kingdom

Pursed with Upgrad

INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMNT TECHNOLOGY

Apr 2020 - Feb2021

Post graduate in Management Studies (Distant Education)

Ghaziabad

Pursed with Upgrad

VLB JANAKIAMMAL COLLEGE OF ARTS AND SCIENCE

Mar2011- Mar 2013

Bachelors in Commerce

Coimbatore

PROJECTS

- A study conducted on Work from Home Advantages and Disadvantages on behalf of the MBA
- A survey was taken on those willing to WFH and those willing to work at office for 50 students Set of questionnaire was prepared with the help of google forms
- With the help of linear regression the calculation proved that those willing to WFH were more in number and hence the analysis of the study proven were accurate.

INTERNSHIP

UAE Exchange Mar 2016 - Jun 2015

Project in Finance and Accounts (Business Compliance Checklist)

Abu Dhabi